テテテテテーン
- こんばんは!
- はい!
- お見合いしたいことがありますか?
- 何だ?
- 大神宮の下にお店があります。
- お店の下で見合いしたいのか。
- あ、これです。
- 酒を飲みましょう。
- はい。
- お酒は酸味ですか?
- 酸味ではなく異常な味である。
- 酔った酒を飲めるにはとてもès gene!
- 離陸!
- ゆそ!
- そこに神様がいます。
これは異常な味です。
- いただきます。
- すごく驚かれました!
- 通常のお店に hauterか!
- が理解でき本尽!
- どけ!
- それを待ってください。
- 早く!
- 皆さんに頼みますか?
- お次はその間に私たちを行ってあげる。
調子が悪くないので、その時間で行いましょう。
-いい consistency?
- No one to drink for the rest of your life.
- This is the only restaurant that gives us directly.
- It's too much for me.
- Let's do it again.
- It starts with %¥ هذه!
- That's a new one and it's tough.
- Sorry, this wine is terrible.
- There are sweet and bitter
- I never had a taste of that before.
- This is a pity.
- What?
- I don't know.
- Of course you don't know.
- Where did you get this wine from?
- I got it from Joshu.
- I've never seen a wine like this.
- What's the name?
- Masamune Kabuto.
- That's a good wine.
- Is this the only one you have?
- I don't have a choice.
- Here you are.
- Thank you.
- How much is the fish?
- Who ate the fish?
- I don't need it.
- You don't need it?
- If you bring me the fish, I'll give it to you.
- You can't just sit there and eat the fish.
- What can you do?
- I can do anything.
- You're fast.
- Are you done?
- I know you're not good at it, but I'll do it.
- Do it slowly.
- What can you do?
- I can do anything.
- I don't care.
- Can you do anything?
- Yes.
- I can't.
- You said it.
- No.
- Do it again.
- I can do anything.
- Don't laugh at me.
- It's just a habit.
- You can do anything.
- I can't.
- I can do anything.